<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Nanosuit</name>
  <author>Mezz, Ogam, Taranchuk</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>Remo.Nanosuit</packageId>
  <description>Introducing the Crysis Nanosuit.

Inspired by the Crysis series, the Nanosuit is brought into the Rimworld universe.

All of the modes/functions use energy which is configurable in the [Apparel_Various.xml] file.
I've made the Nanosuit to be overpowered since the suit is supposed to make a whoever wearing it, a one-man-army.

A LOT of things are configurable via the XML file so if you feel it to be overpowered/underpowered, please customize it to your liking. I believe in the power of customization. Please DO share your settings in the discussions tab.

Primary Functions:

-Power Mode: Accuracy for range and melee is upped, Melee hits are devastating.
-Armor Mode: Absorb any damage (melee, range, explosion)
-Speed Mode: movement speed factor x5
-Cloak Mode: Invisibility
-Symbiosis Mode: Can heal any hediff in an instant.

Secondary Functions:

-Jumping: Can jump/skip instead of walking to do work. (Also works for combat)
-Hack Shield: Can disable any shield (like an EMP) but won't stun. 
-Jump: Can jump/skip to specified location.

Tertiary Functions:

-Night Visor: Accuracy Bonus, No debuff for "darkness".
-Psychic Wave Control: Won't be effected by psychic phenomena. Also charges energy of suit.
-Enviromental Control: Temperature protection range -200~200 degrees. 
-Rebreather: Able to breath in space. (Save Our Ship 2 compatibility)

Nanosuit Stats:

-Armor Rating Sharp: 100%
-Armor Rating Blunt: 100%
-Armor Rating Heat: 100%
-Insulation Cold: 100
-Insulation Hot: 100
-Move speed offset: 1c/s
-Once a pawn wears a Nanosuit, they will not be able to take it off. It's bonded to the wearer.
-Needs surgery to remove Nanosuit.

All the functions can be hotkeyed in [keyboard configurations].

Config options in [mod settings]
-Enable/disable using multiple modes at the same time.
-Option to make [Jumping] to function like the jetpack or skipping like the psychic power.
</description>
</ModMetaData>